<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Qii</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_user">User</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_search">Search</string>

    <string name="search_bottom_sheet_title">Filter</string>

    <string name="label_tags">Tags</string>
    <string name="label_done">Done</string>

    <string name="message_empty">The list could not be obtained.\nPlease try again later.</string>
    <string name="message_please_login">Sign in now to check your personal data, favorite posts, and etc…</string>
    <string name="message_search_empty">Please enter a keyword or filtering.</string>
    <string name="message_success_login">Login success!</string>
    <string name="message_fail_login">Login failed. Please try again later.</string>

    <string name="reload">Reload</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="id_with_at">\@%s</string>

    <string name="long_text">If you have used FrameLayout in your application, then you know that it is a very difficult task to manage views one over the other in FrameLayout. Also, it is advised not to use more than one element in our FrameLayout. The reason behind this is, you have to explicitly handle the motions or you may say the animations of all the views that are present on a particular page of your mobile application.

So, in order to handle the views in a better way, Android introduced a new layout called the Coordinator Layout. By using Coordinator layout you can easily handle and animate the transitions of views present in a Coordinator Layout. To have a clear understanding of the usage of Coordinator Layout, please open your WhatsApp application. Now, open any chat and click on the name of the chat or go to the menu and then click “View Contact”. Here, you will find the profile picture of the user. Now try to scroll down the page. Hey, where is the profile image? Now scroll up. Yeah, you got the profile image? Try to repeat the same scrolling up and down and see the animation. This is done with the help of Coordinator Layout. Another example of Coordinator Layout can be seen below:</string>
</resources>
